<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="receiver_off_button_caption">Start</string>
    <string name="receiver_on_button_caption">Stop</string>
    <string name="local_service_started">Receiver started</string>
    <string name="local_service_stopped">Receiver stopped</string>
    <string name="local_service_label">Audio description</string>
    <string name="notification_content_text">Tap here to open the app</string>
    <string name="notification_ticker_text">Receiving audio description</string>
    <string name="notification_content_title">Audio description</string>
    <string name="notification_channel_name">adOHRi notifications</string>
    <string name="wifi_connection_lost">WiFi connection lost</string>
    <string name="connection_denied">Connection cancelled</string>
    <string name="connection_failed">Connection to sender failed</string>
    <string name="headphones_disconnected">Please connect headphones</string>
    <string name="info_button">Info</string>
    <string name="title_activity_info">Info</string>
    <string name="adOHRi_logo_alttext">adOHRi logo</string>
    <string name="credits">Project lead: Agnes Nuber\nAuthor: Hubert Popiolek\ncommissioned by AG Kurzfilm</string>
    <string name="title_activity_licenses">Licenses</string>
    <string name="licenses_button">Licenses</string>
    <string name="source_code_link">Source code</string>
    <string name="homepage_link">Homepage</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_link">Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="info_text">adOHRi – short films for all!\n\nadOHRi transmits the audio description (AD) of select short film programmes to your ear. This way you can receive the film description directly at the cinema and experience the diversity of short films.\nThe number of accessible short films is steadily growing and more and more short film programmes are being put together by distributors. Ask your local cinema for an accessible screening. The goal is to make short films accessible for everybody.\nBring your own headphones and start the app. The audio description gets transmitted to your mobile device via Wi-Fi. You can control the volume on your mobile device. Thus, you can experience the original film audio through the cinema\'s audio system and the audio description through your headphones.\n\nThe audio description will not play through your mobile device\'s inbuilt speaker. So make sure your headphones are connected. For an optimal experience, bring a charged mobile device to the screening and use wired headphones if possible.\nIn order to optimize reception of the audio description, adOHRi may disconnect your mobile device from the internet until you quit the app.\n\nWhat is an audio description?\nAn audio description turns the film into an aural experience. Settings, actors, facial expressions and cinematography are put into words by professional audio description writers. The visual descriptions for blind and visually impaired audience-members are narrated during dialogue pauses.\n\nThis measure was co-financed with tax money based on the budget passed by the Saxon state parliament.</string>
</resources>